in today's show we're covering the
recent Regional Tournament which is
likely signaling the next card that is
going to be banned in modern the new
SpongeBob secret layers have officially
been spoiled as well as some Final
Fantasy cards being found in the garbage
all that and more in this week's episode
of last week in cardboard jumping into
the competitive news have we just found
the next nardu of the current modern
meta game and I say that because we just
had the Regional Championship take place
at the scg conon in Charlotte USA where
over a thousand players competed and if
you take a look at the top eight you can
see a reoccurring theme grinding breach
shout out to Jesse robkin for winning
the tournament Jesse is regarded as one
of The Originators of the grinding
breach deck dating back to
2019 the goal of the deck is simple have
grinding station in play which is a two
Mana artifact that says tap sacrifice an
artifact Target player puts the top
three cards of their Library into their
graveyard and whenever an artifact comes
into play you may untap grinding station
you then pair this up with underworld
breach a two Manor enchantment that
gives each non-land card in your
graveyard Escape where the cost is equal
to the cards Mana cost plus three cards
you then want to have either two copies
of MOX Amber MOX opal or mistress bble
in your your graveyard and then you can
generate near infinite Mana Mill your
deck and then cast th's Oracle or grape
shot for the win the next ban
announcement is slated for March 31st
but could we see an emergency ban happen
shortly the top two candidates for Bans
are either underworld breach or grinding
station Banning grinding station will
shut this deck down completely otherwise
there's underworld breach which is the
Catalyst for these sorts of combo deck
let me know what you think in the
comments down below turning our
attention to standard let's check out
the current best decks for best of three
on Arena thanks to untapped.gg for
providing this information we can see
that monor red Agro is still dominating
which is to be expected on Arena
following that we have the fourcc color
domain deck which recently took the win
at the Aether drift protour notably the
top Play version of this deck does not
contain any copies of Jace the perfected
mind which is what Matt Nash used to win
in the domain mirror match one deck that
I did want to call attention to is the
blue white omniscience combo deck that's
having a Resurgence the deck looks to
put omniscience into the graveyard and
then return it to play with the four
Mana spell orell's Awakening once it's
done that it uses efficient draw spells
like stock up to dig for invasion of
arvius Loop through a bunch of spells
and eventually create an army of
incubate tokens from Sund the Gateway
and hold up negate to disrupt any board
wipes a real 4D chest deck if you ask me
moving on to product news the SpongeBob
secret lay has been completely revealed
there's going to be three bundles and
these are all reskinned cards no
mechanically unique cards are in any of
the bundles for the legends of B bottom
bundle which contains seven cards we
have SpongeBob SquarePants as jodo the
unifier Patrick Star as random Legend
from Legends bartoo warbeard Squidward
sarcastic snob as grizzl ilth scholar Mr
Krabs Penny Pincher as Cher the Raging
Isle Sandy Cheeks Marshall astronau as
tosy bearer of Secrets Plankton tiny
Tyrant as scr defecto Mite and Gary the
snail as toxil the
corrosive in the lands Under the Sea
bundle it features the five basic lands
with locations featured in SpongeBob and
in my personal favorite bundle the
internet sensation bundle we get six
reskin cards featuring some of the
popular meme moments from the series
with of course now one of the best
counter spell printings in the game
these bundle will be available on March
24th available in both non-foil and
traditional foil for $29.99 and $39.99
respectively of course this is another
while stocks last continuing with
universes beyond the secondary Commander
for the Revival trance deck has been
revealed Celeste run Knight a four Manor
mardu 44 that says when Celeste enters
discard any number of cards then draw
that many plus one and when ever one or
more creatures you control enter if one
or more of them entered from a graveyard
or was cast from a graveyard put a plus
one plus one counter on each creature
you control so would you believe it we
finally broke murderous redcap in more
final fantasy news someone also managed
to find the mangled remains of three
Final Fantasy main set cards a swamp a
card with no discernable features and
what appears to be a two minor black
spell called resentful Revelation
featuring sephos this is not the first
time people have come across magic
products in the garbage who knows if
there's any more of them out there in
actual Magic the Gathering news the
tarir dragon storm story is well
underway with the debut stream kicking
off official previews on March 18th stay
tuned for rules content around the set
once we know more links to everything we
covered down below be sure to like the
video if you learn something and
subscribe because if you don't Wizards
will unban nardu thanks for watching and
I'll see you in the next one